<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Frank Zhang</title>
    <link>https://frankzhang427.github.io/tags/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Frank Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://frankzhang427.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reinforcement Learning in Financial Portfolio Management</title>
      <link>https://frankzhang427.github.io/project/rl_fpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frankzhang427.github.io/project/rl_fpm/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Reinforcement learning techniques have raised attention from financial industry, especially by employing reinforcement learning in portfolio managements. In this project, we explored three state-of-art reinforcement learning algorithms, including policy gradient (PG), deep deterministic policy gradient (DDPG) and proximal policy optimization (PPO). The goal is to train an intelligent agent that can continuously trade in stock market by allocating on different assets. In the course of this project, we performed hyper-parameter tuning and feature selection for each algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classification on Modified MNIST Digits</title>
      <link>https://frankzhang427.github.io/project/modified_mnist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://frankzhang427.github.io/project/modified_mnist/</guid>
      <description>Abstract This project aims to perform a classification task on the modified figures based on the MNIST dataset. Each figure contains two digits and an operator indicated by the first letter of the operation, i.e. ‘A’ or ‘a’ for addition and ‘M’ or ‘m’ for multiplication. Our task is to build a model that correctly predicts the result of the mathematical operation on each input figure. For this purpose, we have implemented a baseline logistic regression classifier, two fully connected feedforward neural networks and a convolutional neural network (CNN).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>